<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Sylvia Moss Martinez</title>
    <link>https://sylviamoss.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Sylvia Moss Martinez</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://sylviamoss.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Understanding and Creating Pseudo-Terminals (PTY)</title>
      <link>https://sylviamoss.github.io/pseudo-terminals/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylviamoss.github.io/pseudo-terminals/</guid>
      <description>This content was written based on Chapter 6 of the Hands-On System Programming with Go book written by Alex Guerrieri.
Introduction Pseudo-terminals, or pseudo-teletypes, are applications that run under a terminal. Many programs are built as pseudo-terminal because it enables interactive use from inside a terminal without needing any graphical interface.
As a software engineer, we use many applications that are built as pseudo-terminal. One of them is the SSH Client.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Criando porta cabos com embalagem de plástico</title>
      <link>https://sylviamoss.github.io/porta-cabos-de-embalagem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylviamoss.github.io/porta-cabos-de-embalagem/</guid>
      <description>Últimamente tenho tentado achar utilidade para as embalagens de plástico que invevitalmente tenho que comprar. Moro em um apartamento pequeno, trabalho de casa, e meu escritório fica no mesmo quarto em que durmo.
Possuo dois monitores ligados ao meu computador, e outros demais dispositivos que requerem cabos, muitos cabos!!! Tantos cabos que deixam meu quarto muito mais pesado do que deveria. Além disso, existem outros probleminhas que uma pessoa com quatros gatos, como eu, pode ter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acceptance testing a SMB client on CircleCI</title>
      <link>https://sylviamoss.github.io/smb-client-on-circleci/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sylviamoss.github.io/smb-client-on-circleci/</guid>
      <description>Background The hashicorp/go-getter library is largely used through HashiCorp products such as Packer, Nomad, and Terraform. According to the library documentation:
go-getter is a library for Go (golang) for downloading files or directories from various sources using a URL as the primary form of input. The power of this library is being flexible in being able to download from a number of different sources (file paths, Git, HTTP, Mercurial, etc.) using a single string as input.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
